

Competences

- Communication Skills
- Leader Ship
- Team-working
- Creativity
- Time Management
- Decision Making
- Problem Solving
- Negotiation Skills
- Good Command English Language
- Very Good Knowledge Microsoft Office
- Very Good at CRM System

Contact

- ★ Elmokattam, Cairo, Egypt
- **■** m_hamdy87@hotmail.com
- **\ +201069277791**

© +201069277791

in m_hamdy87@hotmail.com

MOHAMED HAMDI

SENIOR REAL ESTATE CONSULTANT

Profile

Experienced Real Estate Consultant who is proficient in commercial as well as residential properties. and developing comprehensive property sales marketing plans developing marketing materials and training real estate sales professionals. Specializes in large-scale commercial property and high-end residential properties.

Excellent analytical skills coupled with excellent oral, written, and presentation skills

Strong interpersonal, communication, and problem solving skills Excellent analytical, problem solving, troubleshooting, and decision making skills

Strong ability to clearly document ideas, requirements, results, feedback, and other information in an organized manner during a project lifecycle

Possess cheerful client communication and consultancy skills Superior ability to adapt in a fast-paced and rapidly changing business environment

Experience

2007 - 2008	ADEED CONSTRUCTION COMPANY Human Resources Assistant, Riyadh ,KSA
2009 - 2010	Iberotel Cairo Hotel & Casino Banquet & Catering Sales Clerk, city
2010	Avanti & Kocach Group Sales Executive, Cairo, Egypt Construction company and management consulting
2013 - 2018	Avanti & Kocach Group Senior Business Developer, Cairo ,Egypt Construction company and management consulting
2018 - 2019	Solid Properties Senior Real Estate Consultant, Cairo ,Egypt
2019 - Still	El Mansour Development Senior Real Estate Consultant, Cairo ,Egypt

Course

2007 **ICDL TRAINING**

Adeed Company, Riyadh, KSA

2008 I.T & DEALING AND RESEARCH INTERNET

Adeed campany, Riyadh ,KSA

Education

Bachelor of Laws

Cairo University, Cairo, Egypt